Contact

slevy239@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/samuel-d-levy (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Video Editing
Communication
Media Production

Samuel Levy

Villanova Graduate in Communications

Greater Philadelphia Area

Summary

Experienced Bartender with a demonstrated history of working in the food & beverages industry. Skilled in Communication, Camera Operation, Film Production, Media Production, and Video Editing. Strong operations professional with a Bachelor of Arts - BA focused in Communication and Media Studies from Villanova University. Continuing education through The University of Pennsylvania's Coding Boot Camp for front-end and back-end web development.

Experience

Crowded Castle Brewing Company Bartender

Vizion Group, Inc. Social Media Intern July 2018 - Present Berwyn, PA

Manage social media accounts, Research for National Dog Show Charity Walk.

Quench USA, Inc.
Scheduling Specialist
October 2018 - April 2019 (7 months)
King Of Prussia, Pennsylvania

Riptide Pictures Sound Engineer October 2017 - May 2018 (8 months) Villanova, PA

Recorded interview audio during on-site production in Ghana. Researched historical film during post-production.

So far, The film has been selected for numerous film festivals and has been awarded the best documentary at The Black Film Festival Atlanta and the 2019 Student Academy Awards.

Education

University of Pennsylvania

Certificate of Completion, Computer Science · (2019 - 2020)

Villanova University
Bachelor of Arts - BA, Communication and Media Studies · (2014 - 2018)